Rubin Awale

Web Developer

Mangalbazaar, Lalitpur | 9849085376 | rubinawale10@gmail.com

Summary

Goal-oriented Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutionsoriented problem-solving. Use various web design software to develop customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

Work experience

Smart Innovation

2018 - Present

Web Developer

- Developing & maintaining back-end functionality of the websites.
- Knowledge in building and implementing functional programs.
- Excellent problem-solving skills with keen eye for detail.
- Outstanding knowledge of coding languages, including HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, PHP/Laravel, & API.
- Also have sound knowledge in Nodejs, mongodb, mongoose & Express Js.
- Creating, modifying and maintaining websites as client requirement.

Longtail e-medial

2017 - 2018

Internship

Knowledge of website achitecture

Education

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology

2014 - 2018

Nepal College of Information Technology (NCIT)

Pokhara University

2.8 CGPA

HSEB 2012 - 2014

National Institute of Science and Technology

First Division

Bal Vikas Sec. Boarding School

- 2012

Kanibahal, Lalitpur

First Division

Skills

HTML

Html, html5

CSS

CSS, CSS3



| Javascript |
|--|
| Bootstrap |
| bootstrap3, bootstrap4 |
| Jquery |
| Ajax |
| |
| MySql |
| PHP/Laravel |
| Version Control GIT |
| NodeJs |
| mongoose,mongodb,expressjs |
| Development Tools |
| Sublime Text 3, PhpStrom, Visual Studio, GIT, GITLab |
| Portfolio |

https://www.bigtech.com.np/ http://junglecamp.com.np/ http://arghakhanchi.dohs.gov.np/ http://kulunghomestay.com/ http://asianhotel.com.np/ http://a3media.sinepal.com/

Training Attended

Training session on Developing Applications with MySQL and PHP organized by NIIT, Kumaripati(Voest Alpine Technology). CCNA by Broad Infosys(Tinkune)

Certification

Developing Applications with MySQL and PHP certification from Voest Alpine Technology

Reference

Dr. Roshan Chitrakar

PhD (Information Security)

Associate Professor, NCIT Reviewer of Several Intn'l Journals and Conferences

roshanchi@gmail.com